const daySeventeenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of that house that thousands of Angels do enter it daily and is at the seventh heaven?",
    options: [
      "Baytullah",
      "Baytul ‘Izza",
      "Baytu-d Dhat",
      "Albaytul Ma’mur",
      "Ka’bah",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the prophets of Allaah installed Tolut as the King of Jews?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Daud",
      "Prophet Sulaiman",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Musa",
      "Prophet Ayub",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "The Prophet born without a father is …………………………",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam",
      "Prophet ‘Issa",
      "Prophet Ilyas",
      "Prophet Idris",
      "Prophet Musa",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who will be the first to get dressed on the day of resurrection?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam",
      "Prophet Nuh",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Ya’qub",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the old name of Madina?",
    options: ["Mekka", "Bakkah", "Jazeeratul Arab", "Yathrib", "Baqi’"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who among the Prophets did Allaah test with fish?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Yusuf",
      "Prophet Nuh",
      "Prophet Zakariyah",
      "Prophet Yunus",
      "Prophet Dhul Kifl",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Prophet Ibraheem (May the peace be upon him) circumcised at the age of……………",
    options: ["120", "83", "80", "75", "93"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who first speaks clear Arabic while he was 14 years old?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Isma’eel",
      "Prophet Salih",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Lut",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first Murderer on earth?",
    options: ["Qaabil", "Haabil", "Iblis", "Namrud", "Fir’aun", "Hamana"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the prophet of Allaah that did fast a day and break a day?",
    options: [
      "Prophet ‘Isa",
      "Prophet Daud",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Ayub",
      "Prophet Muhammad",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "There is no one on earth except that he/she had made a mistake or intends to commit sin except a prophet of Israil, what is his name?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Dhul Kifl",
      "Prophet Ilyasa’",
      "Prophet Zakariyah",
      "Prophet Yahyah",
      "Prophet ‘Issa",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the first Idol brought to Mecca?",
    options: ["‘Uza", "Manata", "Laata", "Hubal", "Illah"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first to build Ka’bah among human beings?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Adam",
      "‘Abdul Mutalib",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Kilab",
      "Prophet Qusah",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who re-dug Zamzam after the Jurhum tribe blocked it?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Isma’eel",
      "‘Abdul Mutalib",
      "‘Amru bn ‘Aamir bn Luhayi Al Khuza’iy",
      "Kilab",
      "Qusah",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Shaytan touches every new born baby except……………and ……………",
    options: [
      "Prophet Ya’qub and Prophet Yusuf",
      "Prophet Zakariyah and Prophet Yahya",
      "Prophet Ibraheem and Prophet Isma’eel",
      "Maryam bint ‘Imran and Prophet ‘Isa",
      "Prophet Daud and Prophet Sulaiman",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
];

export default daySeventeenQuestions;
